Thank you for watching!
Good morning.
Today, we are going to challenge
drawing.
She is good at drawing.
Really?
She is a good painter.
What?
She is a painter.
She is a fan of idols.
Have you ever thought that you are a
painter?
You may have thought that you are a
painter.
I have.
So, I think you can't answer correctly
if you listen to the song and draw
without watching the video.
I think so.
Drawing skill is important.
Drawing skill and imagination.
Leave it to me.
Who is the best painter?
That is wrong.
You three draw pictures and tell me
what you drew.
Let's get started.
Are you ready?
Yes.
There are 8 questions in total.
That is a lot.
Let's start with the first question.
I will do my best.
Let's start.
Singing
What was I singing?
Time's up
The end?
I don't know what was coming out.
Seriously?
I thought it would last longer.
I only got the egg after I got the
break.
What are you talking about?
Can I listen to it again?
I'll only play it once from now on.
Thank you for watching.
We were able to use the copyrighted
tracks.
I'm standing up nicely
The ring-in cracks
I'm rushing to reinforce
Reinforce over there and here
What is this?
Wait!
I don't know anymore
What is this?
It's better to watch the video
It's low
What is this?
Everyone is gone
Please subscribe to my channel!
I can do it.
Wait.
I can't do it.
You look so sad.
You are a penguin.
I see.
We should be creative.
We should do it in our own way.
Let's think about it.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Let's start the second question.
Yes, please.
I can't think of the song.
I'll try again.
Let's bake a rice cracker.
Put it on black beans.
If you pour soy sauce,
the beans will fly out with joy.
It's a little different from the last
one.
It's a living thing.
Tennis.
Can you tell me what it is?
Well, a bear.
Well, a head of a scorpion.
What is that?
What is that? An alien.
You're too quick to erase.
I'll just leave it as it is.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Thank you for watching.
Let's bake a rice cracker.
Put it on black beans.
When the soy sauce is boiled,
Put the beans on it.
Wow!
If I put it on this,
It's so interesting.
Wow!
Please subscribe to our channel.
If we hit their favorite tails my
goodnesses,
I'mma forbid my sailors from pastry's
I was saying sorry,
Huh?
Hairo to ta imo
Yakko to eri
gerek to go
Stop right there,
Get your Pikmis into that
ALL PAWNS
If it hits your infinities
What is this?
Isn't it a snail?
Ah, snail.
Is it a snail?
Cat.
What is this?
Are you wearing sunglasses?
My feet are in the way.
Then, that's correct.
I got stuck in a pond.
I'll help you, rope.
If you pull, I'll pull.
I'll leave it to you.
Nico Nico Sarusan.
It was Osaru-san.
I think I can make a better drawing
song.
Yay!
Let's move on to the next question.
Please subscribe to our channel here!
I made a rice ball.
I'll eat it quietly.
I put too much effort into it.
It's all over the place.
Is there any?
I don't know.
What is this?
It's a super-duper.
I'll eat it.
What do you want to eat?
Gorilla?
Gorilla is cute.
I'll eat it.
What is it?
I made a rice ball.
It's not a triangle.
I was sticking my feet out.
I put too much effort into it.
It's all over the place.
But it's delicious, isn't it?
How was it?
I don't feel satisfied at all.
It's a secret.
Thank you for watching.
A simple chestnut
A plate of chestnuts
A tulip bloomed
Everyone was surprised
Wait, I didn't understand anything
I don't understand anything
I can't understand it
What did you say?
It's like a crane
I'm sorry
It's so casual
A tulip bloomed
Everyone was surprised
Wow, wow, it's a lion
It's really casual
I can't hit it
The movie finished
Let's go to the next one.
OK.
Let's go without getting out of bed.
Don't you put the face down였습니다.
I'm going to sing a song called,
「Zenmai Jikkake no Kokeshi 」
I have four switches.
I can't fall down.
I put my feet on it.
I put a beard on it because I'm not
sensitive.
Balea
Oh!
You've been making a lot of loose
characters.
For the time being, cat.
Mouse.
Ritsuki, just a little.
Flower, flower cup.
What is it?
A big circle.
Then it's a full house.
I'm a Zenmaijikake's clown.
I always have a switch.
I can't fall down, so I put my feet on
it.
I put a mustache on it because I don't
have a can lock.
I'm a Maria Revis.
Zenmaijikake is this way.
It was a mistake.
I was close.
I thought so.
Next.
Thank you for watching.
Mouth is like cat's ears
Raise your tongue
So dotty
Slick
And round
Dot dot dot dot
It seems difficult
Using your mouth is also difficult
What happens if we include cat ears?
Everyone is a cat.
It's like cat ears at first.
It's different because it's like that.
What is cat ear?
It's like a cat's ear.
It's like a mountain's opeth.
I think I got it.
It's difficult.
It's difficult to say.
It's a cat.
I got it!
It's a cat!
I got it.
It's a cat.
I'm glad.
Yay!
Let's play the next question.
Let's go.
One dumpling looks delicious
Two dumplings in the back
If you look closely, it's a donut
The inside is good
Please subscribe to our channel
You're not sleeping enough.
Bacon.
What's going on?
I drank a lot of Megashaki.
There may be.
Maybe this is it.
This is it?
This is it.
Now, everyone is one by one.
Actually, this is the final question.
Please.
Thank you for watching.
One of the oden looks delicious
Oden in the back
What is this?
If you look closely
It's a donut
I like the inside
Kirin
Great!
Rui-chan, correct!
I did it!
Great!
So, Mitsuki-san got 2 points
Pikachu towel
Pikachu towel?
Great!
I got 2 points
You have drawn so far
You remember, right?
You can draw from the beginning
Really?
Can you draw all of them?
Wait a minute
I want to see the result
Really?
I will draw
What is this?
I can't do this.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'm scared.
You are like an old man.
I'm so scared.
I'm going to cry.
I think it's not because of the song.
It's my own idea.
The king of drawing is Ritsuki.
Congratulations.
Please cut this and put it on your
icon.
It's free-material.
Please buy it.
Thank you for watching.
Please try drawing songs.
See you next week.
Bye bye.